Mohamed Gamal Omar Sayed

Mobile developer (flutter developer)

■ mahooomar53@g mail.com

<u>01050566622</u>

Mansoura (ready to reallocate)

D Exemption from military service

in Mohamed gamal

MohamedGamaal16

♦ gemy 13

PROFILE

Flutter Developer with experience in UI design, API integration, and state management using Flutter Bloc. Mansoura University graduate (GPA 3.44). Skilled in Firebase, Restful APIs, MVVM, and object- oriented programming. Fluent in Arabic, B2 in English. Strong communication and teamwork skills. Ready to relocate.

EDUCATION

faculty of engineering computer and communication engineering

Mansoura university

2019 - 2024

GPA 3.48 out of 4 (B+)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Flutter Developer

At ABS.ai

Created an app and website (LMS) school portfolio . Firebase Firestore and managed with Flutter cubit, responsive interface, local storage, auth, MVVM, and reliable performance.

Jul 2024 - right now

Demo app for B-labn.

Created an website level 1 (LMS) for student and dashboard for teacher.

Flutter Developer

Show certificate Code Alpha

Fitness App click here Github

Created a Fitness app designed to help users achieve their health and wellness goals. Firebase Firestore and managed with Flutter cubit, responsive interface, local storage, auth, MVVM and reliable performance.

May 2024 – June 2024

Quotes App click here Github / video

Developed a Quotes app that offers a vast collection of inspiring and motivational quotes.

Flutter internship

Show certificate TeknoSoft

E-commerce App Climb-Up click here Github / video

Developed Climb-Up to connect users with local brands for a seamless shopping experience. Features responsive UI, Singleton and MVVM patterns, Cubit state management, Paymob integration, and Restful API for smooth backend communication.

Apr 2024 - May 2024

Flutter internship

Zidio company

LocalConnect

is a mobile application designed to revolutionize the way users discover and interact with local brands. By providing a seamless and intuitive platform, LocalConnect connects users with businesses in their community, fostering a thriving local economy..

December 2023 - Apr 2024

SKILLS

Mobile Development skills

- API Integration(Restful
- API)
- Data Management
- State management
- MVVM design pattern
- localization
- Sentry
- Flask
- Docker
- Integrate native code

Error handle

- responsive and adaptive UIs
- Singleton
- payment system
- mockups
- · debugging
- UI/UX design.

Programing Languages

• C++, java and dart.

Problem solving

Good programming problem solving skills.

Database

- · SQL Database
- Firebase Firestore, a NoSQL document database.

Soft Skills

Teamwork -Adaptability Time management
communication skills
Leadership -Negotiation Skills
- Presentation Skills -work
independently - collaboration.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVATES & VOLUNTEERING

Ektifa Association 2023 – 2024 pack and distribute Ramadan food baskets to families in need. Mansoura, - Egypt Engaged in community outreach and fundraising activities to support the association's mission.

- Demonstrated a commitment to social responsibility and helping others.

AIESEC 2019 – 2020

- Follow up with the host entity to ensure the standards are applied correctly with Mansoura, Egypt no issues Creating a survey for the finished interns about their experience.

TECHNICAL PROFICIENCIES

Flutter: Android, IOS and web

Kotlin: Android

LANGUAGES

Arabic — Native/Bilingual

English — Proficient